<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifestyle on Portfolio website for Othman Bensouda Koraichi</title>
    <link>/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifestyle on Portfolio website for Othman Bensouda Koraichi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Airbnb - Regression Model</title>
      <link>/blogs/regression_obk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/regression_obk/</guid>
      <description>AirBnB analytics - Beijing Introduction The following project focuses on the analysis of an AirBnB dataset. A data cleaning has been firstly conducted to ensure reliable data. The output of the is a multivariate regression model that predicts the total cost of two people to stay at an AirBnB property in Beijing for 4 nights.
 Executive summary The dataset obtained from airBnB contained a vast amount of information which allows for the development of a broad range of insights into the operations of airBnB in Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worldbank data analysis</title>
      <link>/blogs/worldbank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/worldbank/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this analysis is to analyze worldbank data in order to get valuable insights about the relationships among the following socioeconomic variables:
 Life expectancy at birth (life_expectancy_years.csv) GDP per capita in constant 2010 US$ Female fertility: The number of babies per woman Primary school enrollment as % of children attending primary school Mortality rate, for under 5, per 1000 live births HIV prevalence : The estimated number of people living with HIV per 100 population of age group 15-49.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aliquam</title>
      <link>/blogs/aliquam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/aliquam/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempus</title>
      <link>/blogs/tempus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/tempus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magna</title>
      <link>/blogs/magna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/magna/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>